There is a buy opinion here and we want to buy
ICICI Lombard on which we have
buy interest. This has been a hobby for a long time, for
about one and a half to two months, we have been
seeing consolidation in it and now we feel
that it is fully prepared to give the next move
for medium to long term, on an
inch above, so I have made
heavy purchases on Loot for medium term and long term, that is the
product
[Music]
so
ultimately the technical structure is
in good condition, we are noting, what is the matter, it is
Matches Shetty and the targets are quite high,
so here we are
giving spread opinion for two targets, the first target is
1750, the first target is 1750, the
second target is 1999, for both these targets,
buying is being done on this side on ICICI Lombard.